fullcompass.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Statement | Full Compass Systems

#### What Information Do We Collect?

  * **Information That You Provide Us** We store any information that you submit on fullcompass.com or by any other means. For example, you may provide personal information when you place an order, enter a giveaway, request a publication, or contact us. This information may include name, address, phone numbers, email address, credit card and payment information, and other personal information.
  * **Web Site Use Information** We collect and analyze technical information about how customers interact with fullcompass.com including, but not limited to, IP addresses, browser types, operating systems, pages viewed, links, dates and times, and other information.
  * **Cookies** Like many websites, we utilize a standard technology called "cookies" to differentiate you from other shoppers and to store and retrieve information about your interaction with the website. As part of this activity, fullcompass.com participates in the Google Analytics program. [Click here to learn more](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ads/privacy-policy.html).
  * **Email Information and Contact Forms** We may collect, store, and use any information that you submit via email or any of the forms on our website. We may also collect information about email communications such as whether an email was opened or which links were clicked.

#### How We Use Collected Information

Full Compass Systems is committed to your privacy and compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), a new EU data privacy regulation that will go into effect May 25, 2018. The regulation is designed to give EU citizens more control over their data and to unify a number of existing privacy and security laws under one comprehensive law.

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information Full Compass holds about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, rectified, exported, updated, or deleted.  
If you would like to exercise this right, please notify us through the contact information below.

We use collected information for the purpose of administering our business activities such as completing and tracking orders, customer service, administering giveaways and other promotions, customizing the shopping experience, troubleshooting, improving the website design and functionality, etc. From time to time, we may send you promotional messages by mail or email. You always have the ability to opt out of such communications.

#### How We Continue to Market to You

We employ a marketing technique called "remarketing," which allows third-party vendors, including Google, to show our ads on sites across the Internet. These vendors use cookies to place ads around the Internet based on a customer's visits to our Full Compass website. You can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting their Ad Settings. You can also opt out of all third-party vendors' use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

#### How We Protect Your Information

In order to protect your information, we have put in place appropriate electronic, physical, and procedural safeguards. We utilize standard encryption and security technology to protect data transfer, and our information systems are treated with the highest regard for security. In addition, we limit access to customer information to only authorized personnel.

#### Your Order & Fraud Protection

In the event of a criminal investigation or suspected illegal activity, we may be required by law enforcement agencies to share certain personal information.

Because we are interested in protecting you from credit card fraud, all orders are subject to review by our fraud detection department. As part of this review we may require that your order ships to the billing address of your credit card or an authorized alternate address. We may also need to call or email you to further clarify any questions we may have.

The billing address of your card is the address that your monthly statement is mailed to. It is important that you provide us with this address correctly because we use it during our verification process.

If for some reason you cannot have your order shipped to your billing address, you may contact the card company and have them add an alternate authorized address to your account. We will be able to verify this address when we process your order.

Most banks will not allow an alternative address to be added to your debit card. If you need to have your order shipped to an alternative address we encourage you to not use a debit card.

Please feel free to call us if you need any special accommodations regarding your order and we will do our best to help you.

#### How You Can Review or Correct Your Information

To review or correct your personal information, or to change your communication preferences, please call us at 800-356-5844. Your Sales Professional will be glad to help. You may choose to stop receiving promotional communications at any time. Click here if you wish to unsubscribe from any of our email newsletters..

#### Links to Other Websites

Full Compass Systems is not responsible for the content or practices employed by other websites fullcompass.com may link to. When you use a link to go from fullcompass.com to another website, our privacy policy is no longer in effect.

#### Your Consent

By using the fullcompass.com website you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this policy. If we change our policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

### We Are Here To Help...

This policy was last updated on July 27, 2015. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please call us at 800-356-5844 or email [webmaster@Fullcompass.com](mailto:webmaster@Fullcompass.com).
